[Music]
Friends with beer.
You look confused, Peter.
What the hell was that?
That was friends with beer.
Yeah, I know, but that's new.
Yeah.
And therefore I fear it.
Okay. Friends with fear. Whatever.
Much better.
All right, we're here with friends with beer.
We're here for friends with beer. We're here-
I'm doing this is already weird for me.
Can you see why? Two friends with beer. Can you see why by looking at your picture in front of you?
Well I can see you for one thing. Right, but what's different? You're sitting down. Yeah,
I never do that when we podcast. But I just, it was one more thing that, look, I have been failing
so hard today. I was like, I'm not going to bother taking time to adjust my desk up. That's it, Mr.
Scott Willsey is not going to take this podcast sitting down. Well, I guess today he is. No,
No, I thought you were gonna say that's it. You're not gonna podcast me because I'm not taking it seriously.
I mean, I could.
Or in the words of Coach Beard...
I don't want to drink with someone that selfish.
I thought that's what you were gonna say.
On that note, we should get to the beers. But before we get to the beers, we should introduce ourselves.
Okay, you are Peter of the Nikolades, actually known as Peter...
I am Peter Nikolaidis. I am your host, Peter Nikolaidis. And with me is my co-host, Scott Wilsey.
Next time, you can be the host and I'll be your co-host.
Is this your iPhone?
And I'm looking at you on... That's why the image is so good.
You're seeing me on my Mac, that's why it looks like hell.
And because it's dark in here.
But you still look better than when I'm on my
Asus whatever monitor.
You look better than me when I'm using my Windows
attached monitor garbage.
I don't know, Peter, you're a very handsome man.
I would dispute that.
Fair enough.
So let's get to the beer, shall we?
Show me your beer.
I am starting today with a,
I forget the name of the brewery.
Blah, blah, blah.
Jeez, okay.
I know the name of the beer.
I just don't know the brewery name.
What is this?
Ah, I don't know.
Oh, 21st Amendment.
21st Amendment Brewery.
Okay.
And it's Hell or High Watermelon.
It's a watermelon wheat beer.
That sounds good.
It does.
Have you had one of these before?
I have had one of these before,
but it's been a while.
It's been a while.
So taking a cue from you,
when I went to the store,
I bought something that I haven't had before
For this podcast. Apparently I'm gonna say everything three times in a row now
So here's what I have. How many of these have you already had?
None. I have a gigantic brewing which is a Portland brewery project Pilsner crystal
Okay, I like it I have never what is it I don't know I mean it's a crystal beer a pistol
Pistol pistol beer Pilsner crystal. That's great. Not even one sip down and already I can't talk. Yeah. Well, here's the problem
I was going to tell you about this.
So I may let me know if you can tell after I've been drinking this,
because here's why I went deep into calorie debt already before my day even started,
because at midnight I was done with my workouts and I was getting ready to go take a shower.
And I decided to have a cup, as in the measuring unit, a cup and a quarter of Tillamook's
finest monster cookie and cookie dough ice creams.
Ooh. And so that right there was 480 calories.
Sure. And then this is 300 calories. So already I'm 780 calories down.
Got it. So what I'm saying is I've had very little food so far today,
and so this is probably going to affect me. So I went on a 10k trail run right before this,
but I made sure to eat food as soon as I got back.
I exercised before I did this and I ate nothing afterwards.
Right. I did not want to be that guy. Right. So I actually ate first. So that's good though. For
For once, let the beer hit you harder than me for a change or maybe faster.
No, no. You've never been like this, Peter.
Yeah, but I got questions that need answering.
First, have you seen my keys?
That was my only question.
Oh, wait, I got another question.
Can you start my car?
I mean, I feel like that at work some days.
Oh, my God. My last week was so bad.
I was so unproductive. I was useless.
My, I, people come to us with security requests and like, we need you to add this system to the network.
And we ask basic questions like, what is the business purpose of this?
What sort of data does it handle? Does it handle patient data?
And they're like, I don't know.
I thought you were gonna say, what is the network?
Wouldn't surprise me.
So, but, yeah.
As you can guess, Monolith 3000 locks down there because we have a production network and then we have the
normal office networks and they don't like even on the different subnets of the
manufacturing network they don't like things to talk to each other. What a novel concept.
And so what they've done in the past right now we don't have port security enabled on our
particular tools but in the past they've done that and there were some tools that I installed
that are actually right next to us now that I installed many years ago and what they did was
they just enabled port security on everything so that all packet transfer failed and then we had
to tell them which of those packets bouncing off their firewall was ours and which ones were
important to us yeah and we had literally literally packet by packet we had to explain
this is ours this is why it's trying to go to that particular port this is you know it was just
unbelievable that's one way to do it that is definitely a way to do it
deny all okay now prove that you need to let us allow some
Oh goodness. Yeah. Yeah that's um that is a way to do it. I don't think that's the way I would do it.
But that's a way a way to do it. So far my verdict on this is it's quite good. Um my hell or high
watermelon is very good. This is not too hoppy like an this is definitely not an IPA. This is
definitely a pilsner. It's no no it's a pilsman. Yeah yeah but I've had some that claim not to be
IPAs that are still a little hoppy for my taste. This one is not. Well right I mean just because
you're not an IPA does not mean you can't be hoppy. Right. Be hoppy. Don't worry, be hoppy.
So I suggested a silly topic for today, like little things that make you smile. Okay,
here's one that makes me smile. Right now I'm looking at you and I'm thinking,
look at you in there, looking like a brunette Oscar the Grouch. You are, I don't have, that's,
you're not really looking like Oscar the Grouch. For one thing, he doesn't have spectacles like
that right well there's that so what makes you smile peter oh your topic is going to be the exact
opposite of mine okay hmm maybe we should do mine for a beer sides sure okay go ahead what makes you
smile excuse me i had to burp wow that's soon that's sudden you you better talk fast and talk
now before before you do sound like the guy with the car keys silly things so my car has tire
pressure sensors like every modern car now. Sure. Do they actually look at the actual tire pressure
or do they just look at the velocity of the wheel at a given speed and calculate the circumference
of the tire based on that because I have no idea because the ones on my wife's car calculate their
circumference of the tire. I know that mine says you have to drive it for it to take a reading so
So does that affect my answer?
That probably means it's not actually looking at just the pressure, it's probably actually
calculating it.
Probably.
Yeah.
That'd be my guess.
I guess it's cheaper to do or something.
I'm sure.
Whatever's cheaper, that's the way they're going to do it.
Funny today though, I was driving and one of my tires pressure was 46.
No, one was 47, one was 48, one was 49, and the other was 50 PSI.
That just, I was like, that's so funny.
That is hilarious.
I don't know why.
Yes.
Could you feel the tilt?
I could not feel the tilt, no.
Okay, you are not you could never be a race driver I guess is what I'm trying to say.
I guess not.
Yeah.
Yeah, so we can't get the for some reason even though we've done everything that we're
supposed to do, we can't get the ones on my wife's car to reset properly. The tires are
perfect man, I filled them all myself. I got a compressor in the garage. I waited till it
was nice and cool. I filled them all to the exact same they were a little low but I
I don't know how to reset it. It doesn't want to reset.
Got nothing. Take it to the dealership. Pay lots of money.
I don't want to do that.
How's your beer?
Uh, the beer's good. It's still good.
Good.
I'm gonna drink it slowly.
So, what makes you smile? What's a little thing that makes you smile?
What makes me smile? My cat makes me smile.
Because my cat...
Cat's a little thing.
Yeah. First of all, my cat is a badass. I've discussed that before.
So playing with him, just playing with him is fun.
When you pet him or touch him, he's just got this solid feel to him.
Like he, you know, he just feels like a righteously built animal.
But then the funny thing about him is his response to everything in life is biting.
He shows love by biting.
He shows anger by biting.
He shows play by biting.
He shows eating food by biting.
I mean, everything is biting.
Well, some of those make sense.
Some of those do make sense.
But the one where he just he's so happy when he's biting your face or something like that.
And it's like, okay, little dude.
But he's, he's pretty smart.
He like, he wants to use my indoor.
I have indoor shoes that are basically slippers, Adidas slippers.
And they've got this, I thought you were going to say indoor plumbing.
They've got a big strap across the front of the foot.
They're not like thongs, but they're like sandal, like you'd slip on.
And he knows that he can use those to dig his claws into versus
when I'm just wearing my socks.
And sometimes he'll come up and he'll look at my feet and he's about to extend
And then he realizes oh, he's just wearing socks and then he stops and walks away. It's hilarious. Oh
He's not wearing his armor right or the difference between jeans and say my they're like sweats
You know what? I mean
sweats gotcha, but not
Not the old gray Hanes ones with the cuff at the bottom like Rocky wore when he was yelling
Anyway, he can tell the difference and he doesn't hurt me when I'm wearing one and he does doesn't hurt me when I'm wearing the
Other because it's thicker. Anyway, that's what makes me smile. Yeah, excellent. Excellent
All right. How's your beer lasting? Mmm. I'm down to maybe like how I'm more than halfway through
this is my first I have more because
As you can see the bottle is uh, what is it? I made hit to today too dark in here to see
16.9 16.9 fluid ounces. All right, mine's 12. Yeah, you definitely need another one
Just a can. And it's only 4 point some odd percent. I have no idea. It's weak.
Oh, that's true. Yeah, what is this? I dare you call it weak. This is 5.2.
It's not the strongest, but it's not super.
Yeah, you're ahead of me. No, this was like 4.8 or 4.7 or something. So I have a backup.
Yeah, but that looks like something that would be amazing in the summer.
It's pretty amazing and it's summer. So yeah.
By the way, I don't know if you noticed, I don't know if you listened to our podcast, but
I actually put pictures and links to the beers that we drink last time in the chapter arts.
I did not notice.
I did listen to our podcast, but I did not watch it.
So I did not see the links.
What about reading it?
Did you read it?
I would have put the link.
I did not read our podcast.
No.
[laughter]
Although this beer is starting to hit me, so I'm starting to feel like maybe I should
go read a podcast tonight after this.
Yeah.
Lay in bed and read a podcast.
Yeah, exactly.
So I'll do that again this time.
So anyway, from now on, starting last episode, people can look at the chapter art.
They can read our podcast.
They can look at the chapter art.
I will put chapters in there with links to the beer that I have and the beer that Peter
has separately so that people can join us belatedly.
I like it.
Yeah, that sounds good.
But yeah, I think when I go to a Whole Paycheck or Whole Foods or whatever it's called, I
will you know buy something different once in a while. I mean there may be some repeats
but it's not gonna be like I was early on in this where I was always drinking the chocolate.
You're not gonna just do a Budweiser every single episode?
The chocolate porter.
You can mix it up. You can do Budweiser, you can do Bud Light, you can do Bud Light Lime.
Have you ever had any of those beers? I'm sure you had when you were younger.
I may have had a Budweiser a long time ago.
I definitely had a Miller Lite about
seven years ago.
I was out with a friend and his lesbian
wannabe girlfriend.
Wait a minute.
Which made me hilariously...
That was another little thing that made me smile.
Wait, why do you say that?
Did she say she wanted to?
Because he was hitting on this girl and she was a self-proclaimed lesbian.
So we were there and he got this, you know picture of Miller Lite and I tasted something
I was just like my god, this is horrible. Oh, you're way ahead of me. No, I'm way ahead of you. I topped off again
I didn't drink all of the first glass. I topped this off. I thought you were
Toasting to Miller Lite. No, no, no. So no 16 but 16.9 ounces is like one and a half of these cups got it
I've got like less than four ounces in my beer left
But anyway, so the reason I bring that up is that like after he gave up on her like six months later
She married a dude
So I was just like maybe she just wasn't that into you. I don't know. I was gonna say anyway
She was a smoker. So as far as I was concerned no deal. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I told you about the story when my daughter was little right we pulled up next to this guy and
her uncle my wife's brother was infecting her with the
So there's two universities around here. One is OSU, Oregon State University, and there's U of O, which is University of Oregon.
The University of Oregon is the Ducks, OSU is the Beavers, and he is a Beavers fan, so he would infect her with the anti-duck hatred.
And so whenever she would see the green O on somebody's car, she would say, "Duck lover!"
And so one day we pull up beside this guy, it's hot and it's hot, it's summertime, windows are down.
First of all, she's little, so she's sitting in the back behind tinted windows where he
can't see her.
She's in her booster seat back there and she goes, "Duck lover!
And smoker!"
And he just looks over at me.
He looked at me like he was going to climb through his window into mine and choke me
to death.
And I was like, "You know, I really can't blame you, but she's got some points there,
buddy."
So you have Amazon Prime, right?
Yes.
And so you have Amazon Prime Video.
Which you probably never use because you're an Apple TV user, right?
No, I use a...
You can watch Amazon Prime Video on Apple TV.
I know you can, but I also know that you're like this Apple lover.
And you know, you're kind of a purist.
Most of the stuff I watch isn't on Apple TV.
I mean, most of the stuff I watch is not...
Everything we watch is on our Apple TV, the physical device.
But not the service.
Right. Most of it's on Netflix or Hulu.
Hulu's our live streaming TV.
Got it. Well, anyway, on Amazon Prime,
the newest Russell Crowe movie was released really like made
just for Amazon Prime, like Amazon studios.
It's called Unhinged and Russell Crowe plays
an unhinged ex-husband.
Are you sure he's not just playing himself?
Isn't he the guy who beat someone up with a telephone
or threw a phone in a hotel lobby or?
Could be, could be, I don't know.
But it opens with a pretty strong scene.
But then the scene where the protagonist gets involved starts with a scene very
similar to what you just described minus the ducks. It's pretty funny.
Yeah.
It's basically a road rage, a road rage movie with Russell Crowe as the bad guy.
I mean, I was like, you know, I would normally apologize, but she's right.
There you go.
Uh, uh, duck lover. Yeah. I mean,
she didn't say it was bad, but smoke.
Well, the tone of her voice said it was all bad. She was very disgusted.
Yeah. Kids have a way of duck lover, duck lover, and smoker.
That's one of the things like when I see like an attractive woman,
there are a couple of things that are immediate turnoffs.
One of them is a wedding ring. Another would be a cigarette.
And then, I guess I saw this once in an HR handbook,
bizarre piercings or tattoos.
What does that mean?
So that is so subjective.
I guess it's up to interpretation.
It is totally subjective.
I saw a waitress, not really waitress,
like clean up help staff at Shake Shack a few days ago.
We don't have a Shake Shack.
Shake Shack's like a burger joint.
Yeah, we don't have it.
Okay, well we do.
I think it might be an East Coast thing,
maybe even a Northeast Coast thing.
Damn it, Peter.
But she had a pierced frenum and she did it herself.
Oh, ouch.
So like when she smiled and bared her fangs,
or you saw this like inverted horseshoe thing
hanging down in front of her two incisors.
And I looked at it and I was just like,
yeah, that's not a turn on at all.
Not attractive.
Yeah, that's fine.
I mean, look, people should do what they wanna do.
I didn't tell her, "Hey, rip that off. It's gross."
You know, it was just like...
You and I are not people who believe
that women's goal in life should be to be attractive
to all men and do whatever makes men happy.
Like, you know, the old thing of you should smile more
does deserve a punch in the face.
Let's be honest.
I think everybody should smile for,
But... for, smile more, the beer.
Right, but telling a woman to smile more,
that is just like, you're here for my amusement.
You must smile so that I can feel happy about you.
I think I should smile more.
Right. But that's not why men say that to women.
Correct.
So anyway, but the point is you're, yeah,
you're just not attracted to the piercings in that way.
Or in that location.
There are some things that you should not buy
the self-install kit for.
That's all I'm going to say.
No, no. You're going to say more.
No, that's it.
That's one of them.
Well, give me an example.
Well, what you just talked about.
Don't buy the self-install kit for that.
Oh!
The self install kit for front end piercing. Got it. Got it.
Okay. Yeah. I'm good. I thought you were going to talk about like,
Get them if you want them, but let the professionals do it.
Yeah. I thought you were going to say something like, you know,
Wemo light switches or something.
No, no, no, no, no. Install all those all yourself all you want,
but don't do the body piercings by yourself. Let the professionals do it.
Make sure they burn their instruments in fire first and then
So they scald themselves when they go to pick them up.
And then they burn you when they stick them in because they're still hot.
So I got my latest certification last week.
What is your certification?
Amazon Certified Cloud Practitioner.
The most entry level basic junior AWS.
What does that even mean? You're a practitioner of the Amazon cloud.
It means I can tell you about the basics of most of the Amazon cloud services,
AWS services.
All right, well, I can tell you about the basics too. Here it goes.
It is a cloud service that a lot of different companies and people use and a lot of services use.
And any time AWS goes down, 99% of the streaming services or anything useful that you use on the internet is down.
There, that's it.
That's pretty good. Pretty good.
The stuff I learned is slightly more useful and applicable to business.
Oh, that hurts, Peter.
I'd said slightly.
Throw me a fricking bone here.
So for example, there's this service called AWS Athena.
OK.
I've heard of it.
Which I learned about and was able to, like, the next day
apply to one of my clients.
It was pretty cool.
It's a service that lets you conduct
SQL queries against data files stored in Amazon S3.
As you should.
There you go.
And as it happened, I had a client who said,
we have a bunch of data in S3.
and our customer wants to access it,
but we don't want to give them unrestricted access
to the bucket.
So we suggested maybe we can import the data
into MySQL for them,
but now you have yet another point of entry or egress
for the data in the cloud that needs to be secured.
And I was like, but you could give them access to Athena
and then your data is really stored only in one place.
So it makes it a little easier to control.
So that was pretty cool.
I have never used Amazon AWS.
However, I have, Vic and I have played a tiny bit with,
what do they call it?
B2Z, it's the Backblaze,
it's basically the Backblaze version of AWS.
Because we're, 'cause I have a Backblaze account
and we can actually use that and add the BW,
whatever it is, BWZ, B2Z, whatever they call it.
We can use that to back our servers up too.
And as long as we don't actually have a major incident where we have to download all that stuff again, it's basically free.
The costs come in when we start pulling it back down.
Yeah, and AWS, a lot of that is the same. They're a Glacier service. It costs almost nothing to put data into it.
Right.
And they really slam you when you have to pull stuff out of it again.
Exactly, yeah. And so we're going to use it as a backup.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
That's cool.
I'm looking forward to learning more.
I'm studying now for the AWS Associate Solutions Architect.
And then from there,
I'll probably try to grab the Cloud Security Practitioner cert.
So those are my goals for 2021.
Are you a Docker guy?
Do you know all about Dockers?
Not really, no.
I'm gonna start to learn some of that
as part of this, however.
Yeah, I'm starting to think
that Docker sounds like a good way.
Obviously it's meant for deploying stuff, right?
like you have one image, this is how you deploy it
and get it up and running super fast, I get that.
But it also sounds like it would be really good
for just restoring stuff to a known state really fast.
Absolutely.
Yeah, I have not yet doctored much.
I played with it very little, just very, very little.
But I am curious, AWS has two different
like Docker platform things that you can do stuff with,
which I'm like, okay, that sounds really cool,
but I still don't really know what it means. So, I'm new at that.
Peter, I have a suggestion. Can't wait.
Well, no, it's not that.
Oh, I thought it was a soundboard.
I've given up on that. You said no long distance relationships.
[Laughter]
I wish the viewers could see Peter with his head on his podcast microphone right now into his spare.
[Music]
Yeah, there you go.
That's the sound of me hitting my slamming my forehead into my microphone.
If you want to run and grab another one, that's fine.
I think I'm going to do the same myself.
I'm going to go get a 12 ounce though.
This one?
Yeah, okay.
Give me a minute.
I'll be back.
Talk to the listener.
I will talk to you, dear listener.
Scott is going to miss this.
He's not going to hear me opening my Ithaca Beer Company,
Aprica Wheat,
Aprica, Aprica,
Ithaca Beer Company, Apricot Wheat beer.
It says it's a wheat ale with natural apricot flavor.
And the reason I chose this one was number one,
I like wheat beers.
And number two, my grandparents used to live near Ithaca
in upstate New York.
So this reminded me of when we would go visit them
in the summers.
So that's what I'm pouring here now.
So I'm on a kick here.
There's a definite theme to my beers this week.
Fruit infused wheat beers.
Sniff definitely smells a little...
Snuff smells a little apricot-y for sure.
Also the faintest hint of wet dog.
[Laughter]
Wow, that was a weird time to come into that conversation.
I timed it perfectly.
I'm gonna sip this now.
The faintest hint of wet dog.
You know what?
It tastes much more like apricot than wet dog and that is a good thing.
Just show me a bottle please.
Ithaca.
Yeah, so I did explain to the listener and you can catch it in post exactly why I chose
this beard.
I can catch it in post and get the link.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Yeah, I think every podcast should have a little bit of a whiff of wet dog.
Don't spray the mic.
A whiff of wet dog.
That was so close.
Yeah.
Speaking of whiffs, I found a whiffle ball the other day as I was getting out of my kayak.
I can't believe this is what we've sunk to. Okay.
For my kayak run. There was a,
there was a wiffle ball there and I fished it out of the river.
Talk about your kayaking.
My kayak, I bought a Drift Sun Rover 220. I think it's a 220.
It's an inflatable 12 foot inflatable two or one person kayak.
Yes. Yes. And I love it. Okay. It is fun. I've been getting out on it.
I don't know. I'd say maybe a couple of times a week.
I might even go after this cause it's nice and warm outside and I live like a
literal stone's throw from the Mystic River.
So I can just...
carry it right down to the shore...
Wait a minute.
Throw it in the water, jump in, and go.
Uh, uh, uh...
Mystic River?
Yeah.
Wait, do you have Mystic Pizza there too?
Uh, there's probably a Mystic Pizza somewhere nearby.
Are you old enough to know what I'm talking about?
Wasn't that a movie?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
A dumb...
I don't... I don't...
I never saw the movie, but I thought it was a movie.
I won't touch it.
It was a movie.
I used to work in a video store when I was young, so...
Ah, Video Store.
Right.
So here's my second beer, Pitor.
What have you got?
Vanishing Point Pale Ale, and it is not an IPA,
it is an APA.
An American Pale Ale.
Yeah, and I gotta tell you, I've had one of these before,
so I can already give you the review.
Oh, this is by Ghost Fish Brewing Company, actually.
It's a little hoppy.
It's pretty good, it's not as bad
as many of the IPAs I've had,
but it's not as good as the beer I just had.
It's a little hoppy.
Fair enough. But it's okay. So I remember you used to be into, maybe you still are, Russian dash cam videos.
Yeah, I don't spend a lot of time watching those anymore, but they are hilarious.
So I think I've mentioned it. I know I've talked about this on Blurring the Lines.
I don't know if I mentioned it here though, but I pay for YouTube Premium. Okay.
Which is basically just to get rid of the ads. It's very much reasonable. It's justifiable.
It is a justifiable expense.
Yes, cheers to no ads to no ads. Yeah, do the ads be gone of the world? No, of course
Smart folks are now just embedding the ads in their episodes. So yeah like folks. Hey, you know, uh, blah blah blah I use
This vpn provider and you should too and you know, yada yada yada. So yeah, there's nothing like a lame read, right?
So I you know, I move through those. Well, let me put it this way
I'd rather have a lame read by the person doing making the content than an dynamically inserted ad
Yep, agreed. I totally agree because at least I like the personality who's doing it. So there's
some reason for me to pay attention. There's one company or one channel though that I really like,
well I don't actually subscribe to the whole screen rant channel, but a subset of that is
this guy Ryan George and he does a series called Pitch Meeting and it is hilarious. I love it. It
It makes me smile, it's funny, he plays two parts he plays a screenwriter and a producer.
I've seen some of these, yeah.
I like it enough, I'm not wearing it today but I actually bought the t-shirt.
Did you?
And it's just freaking hilarious, I love it and that's like one of the reasons I have it's like,
so I know that I will never see an ad dynamically injected into that. So, I was just thinking about
about that reconsidering like all of my streaming services that I pay for.
Right. I've got Amazon Prime.
I've got YouTube Premium, Disney Plus and Hulu.
I get through my cell phone provider now.
Okay. As well as Apple Music.
So I don't have any of the premiums.
Right. I don't have the but I don't know.
The Disney Plus one includes ESPN access through Hulu, which is bizarre.
Well, they own Hulu now.
Right. They own most of Hulu.
Yeah. Right. Right.
like Jungle Cruise or whatever the new Dwayne Johnson movie just came out.
I don't have access to that.
You have to pay for it.
Right, exactly.
Well, because they're trying to, I mean, they're all trying to figure out how to,
movies that they understand that theater's going away or
at least it's not as popular right now.
Yes.
They've got to charge for access for some stuff.
Or do they?
I mean, they're charging a monthly fee already.
So But Peter,
it would take a long time for that monthly fee to add up to what they were making
the box office. Probably right. So I don't know if like there's a package where you get all the
movies included. I don't have that. That's where I was going with that. But I don't pay for Netflix.
I don't pay for HBO Max at this point. Correct. So although there's stuff on there that I would like
to see at some point. I have Netflix still, but I personally could live without it. I realized I
just don't even use it, but my wife uses it to watch Korean shows. Right. And my daughter
uses it to watch, I don't know what she watches. And I don't pay for Apple TV Plus? I do, well,
it's part of my bundle. You have what, Apple One? Yeah. Right, Apple One. Yeah, because I was
already paying for two terabytes of storage already anyway, and I figured it all out and I was like,
you know what, by the time I add up all these things, the bundle costs the same, I'm not losing
any money and I get the TV and I get the fitness. See, the fitness I would not live without at this
point by now. And that's the thing is like I already have a free membership to the yoga studio
where I teach so I can access any of the classes from any of the teachers there anytime I want.
Yeah. I also pay for a monthly subscription to access to live and to recordings from one of my
teachers that I did all my yin yoga training through. That's cool. So I already pay well you
know I pay for one and I'm entitled to one by my work and stuff so I already have like two other
yoga studios memberships. Although I did a few of the Apple yoga, you know,
Apple fitness plus yoga routines. I did enjoy them. They were decent. Yeah.
I did the ones with, uh, Oh, Jesus.
There's two. I like Dustin and Jessica. Jessica. Yes.
The Australian. Yeah. First time she said, frame your ears.
Frame your ears. And I'm like, what's an is, is that a yoga term?
I literally did not realize she was talking about her ears.
Yeah, no, the accent was kind of funny.
I did, it was a little thing that made me smile.
But I don't know that I can justify doing that.
And the thing is like, I get Apple Music for free now
through, well, quote unquote for free,
bundled in through my cell phone plan.
So like if I didn't have Apple Music, I might be tempted
'cause the only thing I do is I pay for Apple Care,
which is not part of Apple One, right?
That is correct.
pay for extra storage but not the two terabytes. So, you know, I'm paying a little bit of iCloud
storage and that's it, you know, so I don't have the incentive. So, but I will go back
to Apple TV probably in a few months when C has finished season two and then I'll binge
that and Ted Lasso. So, that's what I plan to do.
So far Ted Lasso season two is pretty good.
I saw episode one and I liked it.
Episode two gave me joy because...
Did it make you smile?
Yeah, and I have a episode in the can for Bulbasaur TV
about that episode that I'll edit and release soon,
hopefully, but you can listen to that
to get our feelings on that.
But I feel like it's gonna be a little bit
of a deeper story than I originally thought.
I think they're going somewhere with it
and that's really cool.
I look forward to seeing it in...
October.
Oh, then maybe you don't want to listen to our podcast.
Probably not. Not if there's spoilers.
Damn it, Peter.
I made the podcast with you in mind.
I was thinking about you the whole time.
Well, that's great.
You didn't say that I had to listen to it immediately on the release date.
That's true.
So that'll be fun.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm looking forward to a new Mac when and if they announce them.
Apparently Apple, go figure, Apple is apparently also affected by this chip shortage that's affecting the entire world, huh?
Yeah, of course, but they said they weren't going to be in the conference call.
I thought they said they were not going to be Mac constrained.
They're going to be iPad constrained still, and they're going to be iPhone mostly iPhone constrained.
Yeah.
Which is interesting though, because I mean the big chip, I don't know.
So, so for some reason the M2 or M1X or whatnot is not affected by this?
Well, they make the M2.
Don't they make A whatevers too?
Yeah, but it's not because of their own chips that they're constrained.
It's because of other parts that go into the devices.
Okay.
But not the parts that are going into the Macs.
Apparently.
Correct.
Or whatever.
Well, also the Macs don't sell on the same volumes.
Not like iPhones.
iPhones sell on way more volumes than Macs do.
Even though Macs are having good quarters.
They're selling a lot of Macs, but they're piddling compared to iPhones.
Well, I am looking forward to getting myself a new Mac this year.
And again, that would be a first for me.
New watch, phone and Mac in the same year.
Yeah, I would be. That's big for me.
Spent a lot of money on an iPad Pro.
And that was actually one thing I was doing today was
so I bought a 2020 iPad Pro and I used it so much that I thought when the 2021
M1 iPad Pro came out, I thought, you know what?
gonna buy that because I use this so much that I know now that I want more
internal storage and I want to upgrade to a model of cellular. Mm-hmm. So I said
I'll buy it and I'll trade in my other one. Mm-hmm. They offered me $580 for my
trade-in and I said okay fine. I added it to my order and then I started thinking
about it I thought you know $580 I'm just gonna give this to my daughter and
then my wife can have the iPad Air that my daughter is using now and that'll
last them a long time.
Mm hmm. So I canceled my trade in.
Okay, but I called it in.
They said they canceled it,
but it still showed on my order details
and I thought, okay, I'm not going to do
anything until this thing ships because I
don't want them to cancel my order.
So I waited and as soon as you shipped,
I called him again and this time they
said they cancel it and this time it did
disappear. Here's the problem though.
580 bucks.
So what do you think would happen if
they're gonna if they charged you for
an iPad Pro minus $580 for the trade in and then you cancel the trade in.
They're going to charge you that, right?
You think they charged me twice.
They charged me once on May 23rd and once on June 10th.
And I am going in circles right now trying to get somebody
who cares to take this charge off of my credit card.
It's hard to be the company with the biggest market cap in the world.
So you've got to sometimes you got to just double up on things.
I'm starting to understand how they made 40 billion dollars or whatever it was.
There you go.
Actually I think this quarter was in the 50s, right? 50s, 70s, I don't even remember.
I don't even know.
It's huge.
I did do a brief discussion post on that though in my class that I'm taking in management right now.
And one of the questions was, should Apple take an ethical stance
to try to affect the quality of life of its supply chains workers.
You know, so like people in the mines and people, you know, recycling silicon.
Oh, I think they are.
Things.
I think they are trying to change those gradually.
Right.
Well, the question is, should they?
Like, do they have an obligation to do so?
Well, from a financial aspect, only no.
But from a... yeah, they do.
They have a... yes, all tech companies do.
It's just that most of them don't care.
Correct.
Most of them do not care.
Well, the problem is that Apple is the one that gets called out all the time.
Well, because it's lonely at the top.
Well, yeah, because if you call out Apple on something, people will read your article.
There you go.
If you're just talking about raw capitalism, no.
By the ethics of raw capitalism, no, that's not the point. The point is to make shareholders money.
And caring about the working conditions of people does not make shareholders money.
Correct. And that gets into the whole shareholder versus stakeholder theory,
which I thought was starting to make a comeback right before COVID.
But then it went back to like bat in the hatches and stakeholder defender mode.
What's the difference between a stakeholder and a shareholder?
Shareholder is someone who owns a part of the company.
Stakeholder is everybody with an interest in the company and its actions.
So if Apple was to put a new fab plant in your hometown,
you're going to be affected by that one way or another.
And therefore you're a stakeholder. So taking into consideration,
everybody who has some kind of stake in an endeavor versus,
Oh,
you happen to live near where we're putting a new fab plant and you know,
we're going to pollute the hell out of your backyard and make your property worth
next to nothing and have to leave, you know, for pennies on the dollar. Oh, well, you know,
so that's the difference between stakeholder and shareholder.
Right, right.
Theory.
Yeah.
So, that's one of the things that was brought up in one of my classes that I really enjoyed.
Whew, I am feeling my beer.
I am too. So, you could say that we're shareholders in this podcast, but the people listening
are stakeholders.
They are. They are indeed, but they're not shareholders.
Right.
So, you and I are the only shareholders in this podcast.
Right. We haven't gone public yet.
amazing endeavor that we're making and all the... So popular. So many listeners.
Cash that we're making. By the way, we would love feedback. How can people
feedback us, Peter? They can feedback us at friendswithbeer.com or beer.tweetpack.us
which will take you to twitter.com/friendswbeerpod. No one's ever gonna
remember that but yeah you can do that too. I know. Yeah, yeah exactly. I know. They will remember,
damn it. I had a boss that used to say end all your sentences and damn it.
And I tried to explain that to my daughter and she's like why? And I said it's not about the
swearing. I mean some things I do. It's not about the swearing, it's about he wants people to have
conviction in their ideas. But I just love that. End all your sentences and damn it. Well, on that
On that note, I think it's time we start to wrap up this episode, dammit.
Okay, sounds good.
[Door closes]
I think people that listen to us should definitely tell their friends, don't you?
Tell your friends!
Dammit.
Tell your friends, dammit.
End all your sentences in dammit, end all your beers in dammit.
What are they supposed to tell your friends, dammit?
Mm.
Do you have 10 minutes to record a beer sides after this?
Sure.
Yay, listeners!
What's the difference between a beer sides and a regular?
Well, we so oh!
Remember, didn't I tell you last time?
Here, didn't I tell you last time?
Oh, Vic was like, what's the difference between your beer sides in regular
episodes? And I realized there is no difference.
And therefore, there's no reason to have a beer sides. Yes, exactly.
Let's make beer sides be shorter. OK.
I don't know what like I still don't know what the difference is, but let's do it.
OK. All right. So this episode is wrapping.
This is in the can.
You can't see it listener, but I'm holding up a can.
It's in the beer can.
This episode is in the can.
and we're gonna, as we say on the Blurring the Lines podcast, we're gonna hit the big red button.
All right, here we go.
Only here I don't have a big red button, I just have a blue and white stop recording button.
But I'm gonna put that now at the 45 minute mark. Boom.